Guide to the Stanford University, Press, Archival Book Copies
Stanford University. Libraries.
- 1990
  - Poirer, Richard, Robert Frost, the work of knowing., 1990 (Box 7)
  - Polis, Gary A., editor, The Biology of scorpions., 1990 (Box 7)
  - Re, Lucia, Calvino and the age of Neorealism: fables of estrangement., 1990 (Box 7)
  - Rescher, Nicholas, Human interests: reflections on philosophical anthropology., 1990 (Box 7)
  - Reyfman, Irina, Vasilii Trediakovsky: the fool of the "new" Russian literature., 1990 (Box 7)
  - Richards, Thomas, 1956-, The commodity culture of Victorian England: advertising and spectacle, 1851-1914., 1990 (Box 7)
  - Schirmeister, Pamela, 1958-, The consolations of space: the place of romance in Hawthorne, Melville, and James., 1990 (Box 8)
  - Sherman, D. George, 1947-, Rice, rupees, and ritual: economy and society among the Samosir Batak of Sumatra., 1990 (Box 8)
  - Shimada, Kenji, Pioneer of the Chinese Revolution., 1990 (Box 8)
  - Siu, Helen F., editor, Furrows, peasants, intellectuals, and the state: stories and histories from modern China., 1990 (Box 8)
  - Stein, Rolf Alfred, 1911-, The world in miniature: container gardens and dwellings in Far Eastern religious thought., 1990 (Box 8)
  - Thompson, John B, Ideology and modern culture: critical social theory in the era of mass communication., 1990 (Box 8)
  - Vertzberger, Yaacov, The world in their minds: information processing, cognition, and perception in foreign policy decisionmaking., 1990 (Box 8)
  - Wachtel, Andrew, The battle for childhood: creation of a Russian myth., 1990 (Box 9)
  - Walter, Maila L, Science and cultural crisis: an intellectual biography of Percy Williams Bridgman (1882-1961)., 1990 (Box 9)
  - Waters, Chris, British socialists and the politics of popular culture, 1884-1914., 1990 (Box 9)
  - Watson-Gegeo, Karen Ann, editor, Disentangling: conflict discourse in Pacific societies., 1990 (Box 9)
  - Will, Pierre-Etienne, Bureaucracy and famine in eighteenth-century China., 1990 (Box 9)
  - Wollaeger, Mark A., 1957-, Joseph Conrad and the fictions of skepticism., 1990 (Box 9)
- 1991
  - Baehr, Stephen Lessing, The paradise myth in eighteenth-century Russia: utopian patterns in early secular Russian literature and culture., 1991 (Box 1)
  - Barkan, Leonard, Transuming passion: Ganymede and the erotics of humanism., 1991 (Box 1)
  - Behler, Ernst, 1928-, Confrontations: Derrida/Heidegger/Nietzsche., 1991 (Box 1)
  - Bender, John and David E. Wellbery, editors, Chronotypes: the construction of time., 1991 (Box 1)
  - Bienen, Henry, Of time and power: leadership duration in the modern world., 1991 (Box 1)
  - Blondel, Eric, 1942-, Nietzsche, the body and culture: philosophy as a philogical genealogy., 1991 (Box 1)
  - Bongie, Chris, Exotic memories: literature, colonialism, and the fin de siècle., 1991 (Box 1)
  - Borch-Jacobsen, Mikkel, Lacan: the absolute master., 1991 (Box 1)
  - Bourdieu, Pierre, The political ontology of Martin Heidegger., 1991 (Box 1)
  - Bréal, Michel, 1832-1915, The beginnings of semantics: essays, lectures and reviews., 1991 (Box 1)
  - Brody, Richard A, Assessing the president: the media, elite opinion, and public support., 1991 (Box 1)
  - Brown, Marshall, 1945-, Preromanticism., 1991 (Box 3)
  - Bruyn, Severyn Ten Haut, 1927-, A future for the American economy: the social market., 1991 (Box 3)
  - Carter, Steven D., editor, Traditional Japanese poetry: an anthology., 1991 (Box 3)
  - Coser, Rose Laub, 1916-, In defense of modernity: ns2:role complexity and individual autonomy., 1991 (Box 3)
  - Cummings, Katherine, Telling tales: the hysterics seduction in fiction and theory., 1991 (Box 3)
  - Dalrymple, G. Brent, The age of the earth., 1991 (Box 3)
  - Davis-Friedmann, Deborah, Long lives., 1991 (Box 2)
  - De la Carrera, Rosalina, Success in circuit lies: Diderot's communicational practice., 1991 (Box 2)
  - Durham, William H, Coevolution: genes, culture, and human diversity., 1991 (Box 3)
  - Eisen, Cliff, 1952-, New Mozart documents: a supplement to O.E. Deutsch's documentary biography., 1991 (Box 3)
  - Ellis, Richard, 1938-, Great white shark: the definitive look at the most terrifying creature of the ocean., 1991 (Box 3)
  - Evnine, Simon, Donald Davidson., 1991 (Box 3)
  - Fellows, Jay, 1940-, Tombs, despoiled and haunted: "under-textures" and "after-thoughts" in Walter Pater., 1991 (Box 3)
  - Fernandez, James W., editor, Beyond metaphor: the theory of tropes in anthropology., 1991 (Box 3)
  - Foley, William A, The Yimas language of New Guinea., 1991 (Box 3)
  - Gallagher, Lowell, 1953-, Medusas gaze: casuistry and conscience in the Renaissance., 1991 (Box 4)
  - Gallant, Thomas W, Risk and survival in ancient Greece., 1991 (Box 4)
  - Giddens, Anthony, Modernity and self-identity: self and society in the late modern age., 1991 (Box 4)
  - Goldstein, Avery, 1954-, From bandwagon to balance-of-power politics: structural constraints and politics in China, 1949-1978., 1991 (Box 4)
  - Guest, Stephen, Ronald Dworkin., 1991 (Box 4)
  - Gunn, Edward M, Rewriting Chinese: style and innovation in twentieth-century Chinese prose., 1991 (Box 4)
  - Gutiérrez, Ramón A., 1951-, When Jesus came, the corn mothers went away: marriage, sexuality, and power in New Mexico, 1500-1846., 1991 (Box 4)
  - Held, David, editor, Political theory today., 1991 (Box 4)
  - Hill, Geoffrey, The enemys country: words, contexture, and other circumstances of language., 1991 (Box 4)
  - Ito, Ken Kenneth, Visions of desire: Tanizaki's fictional worlds., 1991 (Box 5)
  - Jacoff, Rachel and Jeffrey T. Schnapp, editors, The Poetry of allusion: Virgil and Ovid in Dante's Commedia., 1991 (Box 5)
  - Jeffers, Robinson, The collected poetry of Robinson Jeffers. Vol. 3., 1991 (Box 5)
  - Kadish, Mortimer R. (Mortimer Raymond), 1916-, Toward an ethic of higher education., 1991 (Box 5)
  - Lai, Zehan, A tragic beginning: the Taiwan uprising of February 28, 1947., 1991 (Box 5)
  - Lamb, Sydney M. and E. Douglas Mitchell, editors, Sprung from some common source: investigations into the prehistory of languages., 1991 (Box 5)
  - Langacker, Ronald W, Foundations of cognitive grammar. Vol. 2., 1991 (Box 5)
  - Laurence, Patricia Ondek, 1945-, The reading of silence: Virginia Woolf in the English tradition., 1991 (Box 5)
  - Leider, Emily Wortis, California's daughter: Gertrude Atherton and her times., 1991 (Box 6)
  - Lewis, Jane (Jane E.), Women and social action in Victorian and Edwardian England., 1991 (Box 6)
  - Lockhart, James, Nahuas and Spaniards: postconquest central Mexican history and philology., 1991 (Box 6)
  - Lyotard, Jean François, The Inhuman: Reflection on time., 1991 (Box 6)
  - Moriarty, Michael, Roland Barthes., 1991 (Box 6)
  - Mücke, Dorothea E. von, Virtue and the veil of illusion: generic innovation and the pedagogical project in eighteenth-century literature., 1991 (Box 6)
  - Murray, Jack, 1930-, The landscapes of alienation: ideological subversion in Kafka, Céline, and Onetti., 1991 (Box 6)
  - Nazzari, Muriel, 1924-, Disappearance of the dowry: women, families, and social change in São Paulo, Brazil (1600-1900)., 1991 (Box 6)
  - Oughourlian, Jean-Michel, The puppet of desire: the psychology of hysteria, possession, and hypnosis., 1991 (Box 6)
  - Pfister, Joel, The production of personal life: class, gender, and the psychological in Hawthorne's fiction., 1991 (Box 7)
  - Rancière, Jacques, The ignorant schoolmaster: five lessons in intellectual emancipation., 1991 (Box 7)
  - Reynolds, Clark Winton, et. al, editors, The Dynamics of North American trade and investment: Canada, Mexico, and the United States., 1991 (Box 7)
  - Schieffelin, Edward L, Like people you see in a dream: first contact in six Papuan societies., 1991 (Box 7)
  - Serres, Michel, Rome: the book of foundations., 1991 (Box 7)
  - Silbey, Joel H, The American political nation, 1838-1893., 1991 (Box 7)
  - Solinger, Dorothy J, From lathes to looms: China's industrial policy in comparative perspective, 1979-1982., 1991 (Box 7)
  - Stafford, William, The Mozart myths: a critical reassessment., 1991 (Box 7)
  - Tavuchis, Nicholas, 1934-, Mea culpa: a sociology of apology and reconciliation., 1991 (Box 7)
  - Toby, Ronald P., 1942-, State and diplomacy in early modern Japan: Asia in the development of the Tokugawa Bakufu., 1991 (Box 7)
  - Tong, James, 1947-, Disorder under heaven: collective violence in the Ming Dynasty., 1991 (Box 8)
  - Van Zoeren, Steven Jay, Poetry and personality: reading, exegesis, and hermeneutics in traditional China., 1991 (Box 8)
  - Vaughan, Megan, Curing their ills: colonial power and African illness., 1991 (Box 8)
  - Wasserstrom, Jeffrey N, Student protests in twentieth-century China: the view from Shanghai., 1991 (Box 8)
  - Wettstein, Howard K, Has semantics rested on a mistake?: and other essays., 1991 (Box 8)
  - Wolff, Jonathan, 1959-, Robert Nozick: property, justice and the minimal state., 1991 (Box 8)
- 1992
  - Allen, Elizabeth Cheresh, 1951-, Beyond realism: Turgenev's poetics of secular salvation., 1992 (Box 1)
  - Amert, Susan, In a shattered mirror / the later poetry of Anna Akhmatova., 1992 (Box 1)
  - Ascher, Abraham, 1928-, The Revolution of 1905: authority restored., 1992 (Box 1)
  - Barrett, Michèle and Anne Phillips, editors, Destabilizing theory: contemporary feminist debates., 1992 (Box 1)
  - Bauman, Zygmunt, Mortality, immortality and other life strategies., 1992 (Box 1)
  - Bernhardt, Kathryn, Rents, taxes, and peasant resistance: the lower Yangzi region, 1840-1950., 1992 (Box 1)
  - Bol, Peter Kees, "This culture of ours": intellectual transitions in T'ang and Sung China., 1992 (Box 1)
  - Borch-Jacobsen, Mikkel, The emotional tie: psychoanalysis, mimesis, and affect., 1992 (Box 1)
  - Borges, Dain Edward, The family in Bahia, Brazil, 1870-1945., 1992 (Box 1)
  - Bunn, George, Arms control by committee., 1992 (Box 1)
  - Bustamante, Jorge A., et. al., editors, U.S. Mexico relations: labor market interdependence., 1992 (Box 2)
  - Cancian, Frank, The decline of community in Zinacantán: economy, public life, and social stratification, 1960-1987., 1992 (Box 2)
  - Champagne, Duane, Social order and political change: constitutional governments among the Cherokee, the Choctaw, the Chickasaw, and the Creek., 1992 (Box 9)
  - Cladis, Mark Sydney, A communitarian defense of liberalism: Emile Durkheim and contemporary social theory., 1992 (Box 2)
  - Coquillette, Daniel R, Francis Bacon., 1992 (Box 2)
  - Court, Franklin E., 1939-, Institutionalizing English literature: the culture and politics of literary study, 1750-1900., 1992 (Box 2)
  - Day Lewis, C. (Cecil), 1904-1972, The complete poems of C. Day Lewis., 1992 (Box 2)
  - Descombes, Vincent, Proust: philosophy of the novel., 1992 (Box 2)
  - Dikötter, Frank, The discourse of race in modern China., 1992 (Box 2)
  - DiPiero, Thomas, 1956-, Dangerous truths and criminal passions: the evolution of the French novel, 1569-1791., 1992 (Box 2)
  - Earle, Carville, Geographical inquiry and American historical problems., 1992 (Box 3)
  - Edelman, Marc, The logic of the latifundio: the large estates of northwestern Costa Rica since the late nineteenth century., 1992 (Box 3)
  - Ehrlich, Paul R, Birds in jeopardy: the imperiled and extinct birds of the United States and Canada including Hawaii and Puerto Rico., 1992 (Box 3)
  - Emmel, Thomas C, Florissant butterflies: a guide to the fossil and present-day species of central Colorado., 1992 (Box 3)
  - Finucci, Valeria, The lady vanishes: subjectivity and representation in Castiglione and Ariosto., 1992 (Box 3)
  - Friday, Karl F, Hired swords: the rise of private warrior power in early Japan., 1992 (Box 3)
  - Galison, Peter and Bruce Hevly, editors, Big science: the growth of large-scale research., 1992 (Box 3)
  - Giddens, Anthony, Transformation of intimacy: sexuality, love and eroticism in modern societies., 1992 (Box 4)
  - Goldberg, Jonathan, Sodometries: Renaissance texts, modern sexualities., 1992 (Box 4)
  - Gordon, Robert W., editor, The Legacy of Oliver Wendell Holmes, Jr., 1992 (Box 4)
  - Greaves, Richard L, Secrets of the kingdom: British radicals from the Popish Plot to the Revolution of 1688-1689., 1992 (Box 4)
  - Hamburg, Gary M, Boris Chicherin & early Russian liberalism, 1828-1866., 1992 (Box 4)
  - Harrell, Paula, 1939-, Sowing the seeds of change: Chinese students, Japanese teachers, 1895-1905., 1992 (Box 4)
  - Henrich, Dieter, 1927-, Aesthetic judgment and the moral image of the world: studies in Kant., 1992 (Box 4)
  - Hexter, J. H. (Jack H.), 1910-, editor, Parliament and liberty from the reign of Elizabeth to the English Civil War., 1992 (Box 4)
  - Hill, Stuart, Democratic values and technological choices., 1992 (Box 4)
  - Ishida, Hiroshi, Social mobility in contemporary Japan: educational credentials, class and the labour market in a cross-national perspective., 1992 (Box 5)
  - Johnston, Richard [et al.], editors, Letting the people decide: dynamics of a Canadian election., 1992 (Box 5)
  - Jones, J. R. (James Rees), 1925-, editor, Liberty secured?: Britain before and after 1688., 1992 (Box 5)
  - Kano, Takayoshi, 1938-, The last ape: pygmy chimpanzee behavior and ecology., 1992 (Box 5)
  - Kaul, Suvir, Thomas Gray and literary authority: a study in ideology and poetics., 1992 (Box 5)
  - Kumon, Shumpei, The political economy of Japan., 1992 (Box 5)
  - Leffler, Melvyn P., 1945-, A preponderance of power: national security, the Truman administration, and the Cold War., 1992 (Box 5)
  - Lima, Luiz Costa, 1937-, The dark side of reason: fictionality and power., 1992 (Box 5)
  - Linger, Daniel Touro, Dangerous encounters: meanings of violence in a Brazilian city., 1992 (Box 6)
  - Lockhart, James, The Nahuas after the conquest: a social and cultural history of the Indians of central Mexico, sixteenth through eighteenth centuries., 1992 (Box 6)
  - Lowy, Michael, Redemption Utopia., 1992 (Box 6)
  - Malchow, Howard L, Gentlemen capitalists: the social and political world of the Victorian businessman., 1992 (Box 6)
  - Manning, Philip, Erving Goffman and modern sociology., 1992 (Box 6)
  - Maryanski, Alexandra, The social cage: human nature and the evolution of society., 1992 (Box 6)
  - Masing-Delic, I. (Irene), Abolishing death: a salvation myth of Russian twentieth-century literature., 1992 (Box 6)
  - Mass, Jeffrey P, Antiquity and anachronism in Japanese history., 1992 (Box 7)
  - Mayden, Richard L., editor, Systematics, historical ecology, and North American freshwater fishes., 1992 (Box 6)
  - Murav, Harriet, 1955-, Holy foolishness: Dostoevsky's novels & the poetics of cultural critique., 1992 (Box 7)
  - Newton, Ronald C., 1933-, The "Nazi menace" in Argentina, 1931-1947., 1992 (Box 7)
  - Olzak, Susan, The dynamics of ethnic competition and conflict., 1992 (Box 7)
  - Pastor Bodmer, Beatriz, The armature of conquest: Spanish accounts of the discovery of America, 1492-1589., 1992 (Box 7)
  - Paz, D. G. (Denis G.), Popular anti-Catholicism in Mid-Victorian England., 1992 (Box 7)
  - Pike, David, 1950-, The politics of culture in Soviet-occupied Germany, 1945-1949., 1992 (Box 7)
  - Poinar, George O, Life in amber., 1992 (Box 7)
  - Raftery, Judith Rosenberg, 1939-, Land of fair promise: politics and reform in Los Angeles schools, 1885-1941., 1992 (Box 7)
  - Reich, Klaus, 1906-, The completeness of Kant's table of judgments., 1992 (Box 8)
  - Robin, Régine, 1939-, Socialist realism: an impossible aesthetic., 1992 (Box 8)
  - Robinson, Orrin W., 1947-, Old English and its closest relatives: a survey of the earliest Germanic languages., 1992 (Box 8)
  - Rosenberg, Nathan, et. al, editors, Technology and the wealth of nations., 1992 (Box 8)
  - Salmons, Joe, 1956-, Accentual change and language contact: comparative survey and a case study of early northern Europe., 1992 (Box 8)
  - Sanderson, Steven E, The politics of trade in Latin American development., 1992 (Box 8)
  - Scully, Timothy, Rethinking the center: party politics in nineteenth- and twentieth-century Chile., 1992 (Box 8)
  - Silverman, Milton, 1910-, Bad medicine: the prescription drug industry in the Third World., 1992 (Box 8)
  - Sitton, Tom, 1949-, John Randolph Haynes, California progressive., 1992 (Box 8)
  - Sugano, Marian Zwerling, 1951-, The poetics of the occasion: Mallarmé and the poetry of circumstance., 1992 (Box 8)
  - Szilard, Leo, The voice of the dolphins and other stories., 1992 (Box 9)
  - Takeuchi, Melinda, Taiga's true views: the language of landscape painting in eighteenth-century Japan., 1992 (Box 9)
  - Tonomura, Hitomi, Community and commerce in late medieval Japan: the corporate villages of Tokuchin-ho., 1992 (Box 9)
  - Ueda, Makoto, 1931-, Basho and his interpreters: selected hokku with commentary., 1992 (Box 9)
  - White, Stephen A. (Stephen Augustus), Sovereign virtue: Aristotle on the relation between happiness and prosperity., 1992 (Box 9)
  - Wofford, Susanne Lindgren, 1952-, The choice of Achilles: the ideology of figure in the epic., 1992 (Box 9)
  - Wolf, Margery, A thrice-told tale: feminism, postmodernism, and ethnographic responsibility., 1992 (Box 9)
  - Wolgast, Elizabeth Hankins, 1929-, Ethics of an artificial person: lost responsibility in professions and organizations., 1992 (Box 9)
- 1993
  - Adams, R. J. Q. (Ralph James Q.), 1943-, British politics and foreign policy in the age of appeasement, 1935-39., 1993 (Box 9)
  - Alegría, Fernando, 1918-, Allende: a novel., 1993 (Box 9)
  - Andrew, Christopher and Oleg Gordievsky, editors, Comrade Kryuchkov's instructions: top secret files on KGB foreign operations, 1975-1985., 1993 (Box 9)
  - Archer, John Michael, Sovereignty and intelligence: spying and court culture in the English Renaissance., 1993 (Box 9)
  - Barr, Nicholas, Economics of the Welfare State., 1993 (Box 1)
  - Berger, Joseph and Morris Zelditch, Jr., editors, Theoretical research programs: studies in the growth of theory., 1993 (Box 1)
  - Brown, Philip C., 1947-, Central authority and local autonomy in the formation of early modern Japan: the case of Kaga domain., 1993 (Box 1)
  - Bucholz, R. O., 1958-, The Augustan court: Queen Anne and the decline of court culture., 1993 (Box 1)
  - Cahill, Suzanne, Transcendence and Divine Passion., 1993 (Box 1)
  - Carnochan, W. B, The battleground of the curriculum: liberal education and the American experience., 1993 (Box 1)
  - Chambrun, René de, 1906-, Mission and betrayal, 1940-1945: working with Franklin Roosevelt to help save Britain and Europe., 1993 (Box 1)
  - Costlow, Jane T., et. al., editors, Sexuality and the body in Russian culture., 1993 (Box 2)
  - Cranston, Edwin A, A Waka anthology., 1993 (Box 1)
  - Derrida, Jacques, Aporias: dying--awaiting (one another at) the "limits of truth" (mourir--s'attendre aux "limites de la vérité")., 1993 (Box 2)
  - Dilts, James D., 1936-, The great road: the building of the Baltimore and Ohio, the nation's first railroad, 1828-1853., 1993 (Box 2)
  - Eitner, Lorenz, Stanford University Museum of Art, the drawing collection., 1993 (Box 2)
  - Fenves, Peter D. (Peter David), 1960-, Chatter": language and history in Kierkegaard., 1993 (Box 2)
  - Filler, Louis, 1912-, The muckrakers., 1993 (Box 2)
  - Fincham, Kenneth, ed, The early Stuart church., 1993 (Box 2)
  - Fischer, John Martin, editor, The Metaphysics of death., 1993 (Box 2)
  - Fliegelman, Jay, Declaring independence: Jefferson, natural language, and the culture of performance., 1993 (Box 2)
  - Folkenflik, Robert, editor, he Culture of autobiography: constructions of self-representation., 1993 (Box 2)
  - Fu, Poshek, 1955-, Passivity, resistance, and collaboration: intellectual choices in occupied Shanghai, 1937-1945., 1993 (Box 3)
  - Fusso, Susanne, Designing dead souls: an anatomy of disorder in Gogol., 1993 (Box 3)
  - Gans, Eric, 1941-, Originary thinking: elements of generative anthropology., 1993 (Box 3)
  - Giddens, Anthony, New rules of sociological method: a positive critique of interpretative sociologies., 1993 (Box 3)
  - Giddens, Anthony, The Giddens reader., 1993 (Box 3)
  - Goncharov, S. N. (Sergei Nikolaevich), Uncertain partners: Stalin, Mao, and the Korean War., 1993 (Box 3)
  - Goux, Jean-Joseph, 1943-, Oedipus, philosopher., 1993 (Box 3)
  - Gwilliam, Tassie, 1954-, Samuel Richardson's fictions of gender., 1993 (Box 3)
  - Hansen, Phillip, Hannah Arendt., 1993 (Box 3)
  - Hatamiya, Leslie T., 1969-, Righting a wrong: Japanese Americans and the passage of the Civil Liberties Act of 1988., 1993 (Box 3)
  - Held, David, editor, Prospects for democracy: North, South, East, West., 1993 (Box 4)
  - Henry, Michel, 1922-, The genealogy of psychoanalysis., 1993 (Box 4)
  - Hewitt, Andrew, 1961-, Fascist modernism: aesthetics, politics, and the avant-garde., 1993 (Box 4)
  - Hing, Bill Ong, Making and remaking Asian America through immigration policy, 1850-1990., 1993 (Box 4)
  - Holloway, Thomas H., 1944-, Policing Rio de Janeiro: repression and resistance in a 19th-century city., 1993 (Box 4)
  - Hsiao, Chien, Traveller without a map., 1993 (Box 4)
  - Jackson, Robert Louis, Dialogues with Dostoevsky: the overwhelming questions., 1993 (Box 4)
  - Janelli, Roger L, Making capitalism: the social and cultural construction of a South Korean Conglomerate., 1993 (Box 4)
  - Klein, Herbert S, Haciendas and ayllus: rural society in the Bolivian Andes in the eighteenth and nineteenth centuries., 1993 (Box 4)
  - Kofman, Sarah, Nietzsche and metaphore., 1993 (Box 5)
  - Krieger, Murray, ed, The aims of representation., 1993 (Box 5)
  - Levinas, Emmanuel, Outside the subject., 1993 (Box 5)
  - Lindsay, Franklin, 1916-, Beacons in the night: with the OSS and Tito's partisans in wartime Yugoslavia., 1993 (Box 5)
  - London, Jack, 1876-1916, The complete short stories of Jack London., 1993 (Box 5)
  - Lorey, David E, The university system and economic development in Mexico since 1929., 1993 (Box 5)
  - Lowenthal, Abraham F. and Katrina Burgess, editors, The California-Mexico connection., 1993 (Box 6)
  - Lower, Richard Coke, A bloc of one: the political career of Hiram W. Johnson., 1993 (Box 6)
  - Luftig, Victor, 1959-, Seeing together: friendship between the sexes in English writing from Mill to Woolf., 1993 (Box 6)
  - Minowitz, Peter, 1955-, Profits, priests, and princes: Adam Smith's emancipation of economics from politics and religion., 1993 (Box 6)
  - Monk, Leland, 1953-, Standard deviations: chance and the modern British novel., 1993 (Box 6)
  - Nancy, Jean-Luc, The birth to presence., 1993 (Box 6)
  - Nancy, Jean-Luc, The experience of freedom., 1993 (Box 6)
  - Netting, Robert McC, Smallholders, householders: farm families and the ecology of intensive, sustainable agriculture., 1993 (Box 6)
  - Palumbo-Liu, David, The poetics of appropriation: the literary theory and practice of Huang Tingjian., 1993 (Box 7)
  - Patch, Robert, Maya and Spaniard in Yucatan, 1648-1812., 1993 (Box 7)
  - Perry, Elizabeth J, Shanghai on strike: the politics of Chinese labor., 1993 (Box 7)
  - Popkin, Cathy, 1954-, The pragmatics of insignificance: Chekhov, Zoshchenko, Gogol., 1993 (Box 7)
  - Quinn, Dermot, Patronage and piety., 1993 (Box 7)
  - Reid, Roddey, 1952-, Families in jeopardy: regulating the social body in France, 1750-1910., 1993 (Box 7)
  - Ricklefs, M. C. (Merle Calvin), A history of modern Indonesia since c. 1300., 1993 (Box 7)
  - Rollins, Reed C. (Reed Clark), 1911-, The Cruciferae of continental North America: systematics of the mustard family from the Arctic to Panama., 1993 (Box 7)
  - Rotman, B. (Brian), Ad infinitum ... the ghost in Turing's machine: taking God out of athematics and putting the body back in: an essay in corporeal emiotics., 1993 (Box 7)
  - Rouzer, Paul F, Writing another's dream: bthe poetry of Wen Tingyun., 1993 (Box 7)